### **Basic Information**

I am a self taught front end developer who has obtained a highly varied amount of experience through a colourful history of careers. I've always had an affinity for coding and natural aptitude to all things computer-related.

I am a fast learner and highly self motivated, but also a strong team member. I can consistently meet any client's needs. My biggest strength is my ability to adapt to nearly any situation and solve problems quickly and effectively.

### Education

University of Pretoria 2008-2013

Masters of Divinity (MDiv) Bachelors in Theology (BTh)

**iT+FE** 2017-2018 Certificate III in Travel

CodeCademy.com 2019

Career Course in Web Development Online course in Python

### Professional Experience

Owner & Photographer - Johan W Photography 2018 - Present

My first foray into professional website creation using WordPress CMS. Also full management of all online assets.

## Travel Agent - Cruiseabout & Flight Centre 2017 - 2018

My first job in Australia. Assisted in migrating and maintaining the Cruiseabout Cleveland database to 4 other stores upon the closure of Cruiseabout over a 2 month process.

# Reverend and Youth Pastor - Dutch Reformed Church

2013 - 2017

Presented a class at the University of Pretoria on the use of computers and visual media in congregations.

Created a custom presentation package.

Go-to IT guy for over 15 churches across South Africa.

# Johan van der Merwe

As someone who enjoys problem solving and analytical thinking, software development is an obvious path for me.

### Personal Traits:

- Self motivated and self taught.
- Able to both work independently and in fast team-based scenarios.
- Highly motivated, dedicated and problem solving.
- Fast learner.
- Able to reach targets and deadlines consistently.

#### Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React.JS
- Python
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Prototyping (XD & Figma)
- WordPress CMS
- Blender 3D

#### Personal Details

johanvdm.teo@gmail.com

github.com/Johanvdm371

johanvdm371.github.io/Showcase\_Site/